Guide to the Papers of George L. Mosse (1918-1999), 1780-2001 AR 25137 / MF 671
Center for Jewish History, Publisher.
- Series III: Correspondence, 1919-2001; 22 linear feet
  - Subseries 3: Personal, undated, 1946-2001; 9 linear feet
    - B) Individuals
      - Hexter, J. H. (Jack H.), 1957, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 82)
      - Hill, Christopher, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 83)
      - Hillerbrand, Hans Joachim, 1966-1968 (Box 35, Folder 84)
      - Hinde, Robert A., 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 85)
      - Hinderer, Walter, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 86)
      - Hirsch, John L., 1960-1966 (Box 35, Folder 87)
      - Hirsch, Helmut, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 88)
      - Hirsch, Rita, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 89)
      - Hoberman, John M. (John Milton), 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Horowitz, Irving Louis, 1975, 1980-1996 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Hoter, Elaine, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Howe, Ellic, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Howorth, Jolyon, 1981-1986 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Hoyt, Robert Stuart, 1949-1951, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Hubert, Inge, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Hull, Isabel V., 1982-1998 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Hurwitz, Roger, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Hutchison, Jane Campbell, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Hutton, Patrick H., 1970-1979 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Hyman, Paula, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Hyman, Ruth Link-Salinger, 1971-1974 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Iggers, Georg G., 1967-1998 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Iggers, Wilma, 1979, 1983, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Jacobmeyer, Wolfgang, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Jacobitti, Edmund E., 1967-1981 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Jacoby, Russell, 1968-1985, 1995-1997 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - Jaeger, Hasso, 1962, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - Jarausch, Konrad Hugo, 1972, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - Jay, Martin, 1973-1987 (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - Jedin, Hubert, 1966-1971 (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - Jedlicki, Jerzy, 1977, 1982-1983 (Box 36, Folder 23)
      - Jelavich, Barbara, 1967-1970 (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - Jelinek, Yeshayahu A., 1971 (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - Jellonnek, Burkhard, 199 (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - Jensen, Merrill, 1956-1957, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - Jerome, Roy, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - Johnson, Eric A., 1996-1998 (Box 36, Folder 29)
      - Joll, James, 1969, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 30)
      - Jonca, Karol, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 31)
      - Junko, Ando, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 32)
      - Kaiser, Nancy A., 1984, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 33)
      - Kamenka, Eugene, 1974-1986, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 34)
      - Kammen, Michael G., 1985 (Box 36, Folder 35)
      - Kaplan, Marion A., 1992, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 36)
      - Karpat, Kemal H., undated (Box 36, Folder 37)
      - Kastenmeier, Robert, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 38)
      - Kater, Michael H., 1972-1997 (Box 36, Folder 39)
      - Katz, Elihu, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 40)
      - Katz, Jacob, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 41)
      - Katz, Ruth, 1986, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 42)
      - Katz, Steven T., 1981 (Box 36, Folder 43)
      - Keck, Timothy R., 1971-1994 (Box 36, Folder 44)
      - Kelly, Alfred, 1970-1977 (Box 36, Folder 45)
      - Kelly, Alfred, 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 46)
      - Kelly, Alfred, 1980-1990 (Box 36, Folder 47)
      - Kelley, Donald R., 1996 (Box 36, Folder 48)
      - Kern, John, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 49)
      - Kern, Stephen, 1972-2001 (Box 36, Folder 50)
      - Kessler, Mario, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 51)
      - Kingdon, Robert M.?, 1993-1999 (Box 36, Folder 52)
      - Kinzig, Wolfram, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 53)
      - Kirchgässner, Bernhard, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 54)
      - Klein, Dennis B., 1981 (Box 36, Folder 55)
      - Kluback, William, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 56)
      - Kluge, Ulrich, 1971, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 57)
      - Knei-Paz, Baruch, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 58)
      - Kniesmeijer, Joke, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 59)
      - Koberstein, Thea, 1997-1998 (Box 36, Folder 60)
      - Koch, Otto and Joan, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 61)
      - Kocka, Jürgen, 1970-1971, 1996-1997 (Box 36, Folder 62)
      - Koehl, Robert Lewis, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 63)
      - Koenigsberger, H. G. (Helmut Georg), 1967-1968, 1973-1984, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 64)
      - Kohl, Herb, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 65)
      - Kohlberg, Etan, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 66)
      - Kohler, Eric D., 1971-1975, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 67)
      - Kohn, Carlos, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 68)
      - Kohut, Heinz, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 69)
      - Kolb, Eberhard, 1978, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 70)
      - Koonz, Claudia, 1987, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 71)
      - Köppen, Maria, 1946-1949 (Box 36, Folder 72)
      - Korey, Michael, 1996-1998 (Box 36, Folder 73)
      - Kornberg, Jacques, 1971-1973 (Box 36, Folder 74)
      - Koselleck, Reinhart, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 75)
      - Kostelanetz, Richard, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 76)
      - Kovács, Mária M., 1995 (Box 36, Folder 77)
      - Krammer, Arnold, 1971, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 78)
      - Kranzler, David, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 79)
      - Kraus, Elisabeth, 1991-1999 (Box 36, Folder 80)
      - Kren, Claudia, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 81)
      - Kren, George M., 1959-1989, 1997-1999 (Box 36, Folder 82)
      - Kreutzer, Helmut, 1986, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 83)
      - Kropp, Catherine, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 84)
      - Kugelmass, Jack, 1991-1994 (Box 36, Folder 85)
      - Kulka, Otto Dov, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 86)
      - Kuntz, Paul Grimley, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 87)
      - Kwiet, Konrad, 1980, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 88)
      - Labisch, Alfons, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - LaCapra, Dominick, 1991, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Lachance, Paul F., 1967-1986 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Lachman, Edward, 1992-1998 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Lacur, Jacob, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Lambert, Nick, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Lamberti, Marjorie, 1967-1978 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Laquay, Heinz, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Laquer, Walter, 1960-1997 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Laquer, Walter - Festschrift, 1989-1991 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Laurence, Frank, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Laurent, Pierre-Henri, 1970-1971` (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Lautmann, R?diger, 1983-1985 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Lavine?, Joe, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Leavitt, Frank J., 1988 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Leberstein, Steven, 1967-1976 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Lebowitz, Gary, 1980, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Ledeen, Barbara B., 1996 (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - Ledeen, Michael Arthur, 1965-1989, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Leed, Eric J., 1991-1994 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - Leibovici, Solange, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - Leidersdorf, Selma, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Leitgeb, Hanna, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - Leith, James A., 1972 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - Lemke, Jürgen, 1991, 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 25)
      - Leoussi, Athena S., 1992-1997 (Box 37, Folder 26)
      - Lerner, Paul Frederick, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 27)
      - Lessing, Fred W., 1979, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - Levi, John S., 1995-1998 (Box 37, Folder 29)
      - Levine, Norman, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 30)
      - Levine, Robert M., 1990-1997 (Box 37, Folder 31)
      - Lewis, Beth Irwin, 1960-1997 (Box 37, Folder 32)
      - Liang, Hsi-huey, 1969-1972 (Box 37, Folder 33)
      - Lidtke, Vernon L, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 34)
      - Lieven, D. C. B., 1997 (Box 37, Folder 35)
      - Lifton, Robert Jay, 1979-1992 (Box 37, Folder 36)
      - Lifton, Robert Jay - Festschrift, 1994-1996 (Box 37, Folder 37)
      - Lin, Yusheng, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 38)
      - Linden, Marcel van der, 1988-1991 (Box 37, Folder 39)
      - Linenthal, Edward Tabor, 1991, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 40)
      - Linse, Ulrich, 1977-1998 (Box 37, Folder 41)
      - Lipset, Seymour Martin, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 42)
      - Littell, Franklin Hamlin, 1975, 1980, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 43)
      - Loewenberg, Peter, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 44)
      - Loewenstein, Bedrich, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 45)
      - Lohmann, Ingrid, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 46)
      - Loizos, Peter, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 47)
      - Lough, Joseph W.H., 1983-1999 (Box 37, Folder 48)
      - Lubich, Frederick Alfred, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 49)
      - Lucchesi, Joachim, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 50)
      - Lunn, Joe, 1979-1998 (Box 37, Folder 51)
      - Lurz, Meinhold, 1985-1988 (Box 37, Folder 52)
      - Lustiger, Gila, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 53)
      - Mackaman, Douglas Peter, 1985-1998 (Box 37, Folder 54)
      - Mackert, Paul, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 55)
      - Madajczyk, Czeslaw, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 56)
      - Magoulias, Harry J., 1966-1970 (Box 37, Folder 57)
      - Maier, Charles S., 1969-1983 (Box 37, Folder 58)
      - Mais, Yitzchak, 1975, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 59)
      - Mandel, Robert A., 1969-1998 (Box 37, Folder 60)
      - Mandell, Richard D., 1969-1973 (Box 37, Folder 61)
      - Mankowitz, Zeev, 1970-1983, 1994, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 62)
      - Mann, Michael, 1994-1995, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 63)
      - Mann, Vivian B., 1993 (Box 37, Folder 64)
      - Mansoor, Menahem, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 65)
      - Marchand, Suzanne L., 1996, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 66)
      - Margaliot, Abraham, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 67)
      - Marks, Harry M., 1993 (Box 37, Folder 68)
      - Marrus, Michael Robert, 1969, 1975-1997 (Box 37, Folder 69)
      - Martin, Biddy, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 70)
      - Martinotti, Guido, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 71)
      - Marwick, Arthur, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 72)
      - Matteson, Robert Eliot, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 73)
      - McCoy, Donald R., 1993 (Box 37, Folder 74)
      - McNaron, Toni A. H., 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 75)
      - Megill, Allan, 1982, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 76)
      - Meijer, Miriam Claude, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 77)
      - Melching, W. (Willem), 1988-1997 (Box 37, Folder 78)
      - Melman, Billie, 1990-1998 (Box 37, Folder 79)
      - Melson, Robert, 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 80)
      - Mendes-Flohr, Paul R., 1979-1986, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 81)
      - Meroz, Ronit, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 82)
      - Messerschmidt, Manfred, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 83)
      - Meyer, Henry Cord, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 84)
      - Meyer, Michael A., 1980-1998 (Box 37, Folder 85)
      - Micale, Mark S., 1995-1998 (Box 37, Folder 86)
      - Michel, Henri, 1968-1969, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 87)
      - Michels, Rainer, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 88)
      - Millman, Richard, 1991, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 89)
      - Milton, Sybil, 1977-1997 (Box 37, Folder 90)
      - Miscoll, Illa and Dan, 1997-1998 (Box 37, Folder 91)
      - Mitzman, Arthur, 1970-1971, 1985, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 92)
      - Mohler, Armin, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 93)
      - Moore, Hilda and John, 1989-1998 (Box 37, Folder 94)
      - Morris, Grant, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 95)
      - Morris-Keitel, Peter, 1994-1997 (Box 37, Folder 96)
      - Moses, Emmanuel, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 97)
      - Moses, Kaethe, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 98)
      - Moses, Stefan, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 99)
      - Mosès, Stéphane, 1976-1998 (Box 37, Folder 100)
      - Mosse, Werner Eugen, 1958-2001 (Box 37, Folder 101)
      - Mühlfenzl, Isabel, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 102)
      - Muller, Jerry Z., 1976-1999 (Box 37, Folder 103)
      - Müller, Klaus, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 104)
      - Nevin, Thomas R., 1991-1994 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - New, John F. H., 1964-1970 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Niederland, Doron, 1983, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Niewyk, Donald L., 1981 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Nipperdey, Thomas, 1979-1987 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Nipperdey, Vigdis, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Noack-Mosse, Eva, 1952-1984 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Noble, David W., 1996 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Nollendorfs, Cora Lee, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Nollendorfs, Valters, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Norich, Samuel, 1982, 19851993 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Novak, James, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Norton, Mary Beth, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Nugent, Donald, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Nye, Robert A., 1971, 1984-1995 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Ohana, David, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Oosterhuis, Harry, 1995-1998 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Orbach, Alexander, 1970-1988 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Orr, William J., 1968-1985 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - Palmesono, Enzo, 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Panzer, Elizabeth, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Papayanis, Nicholas, 1986, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - Paret, Peter, 1978-1997 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - Parker, Andrew, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - Parlangeli, Francesco, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - Passerini, Luisa, 1993-1997 (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - Paucker, Arnold, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 27)
      - Payne, Stanley G., 1992-2000 (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - Pehle, Walter H., 1989-1990, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - Penny, H. Glenn, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 30)
      - Perry, Joseph B., 1995 (Box 38, Folder 31)
      - Petersen, Jens, 1987-1998 (Box 38, Folder 32)
      - Peterson, Brian, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 33)
      - Petrovich, Michael Boro, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 34)
      - Pettegrew, John, 1993-1994 (Box 38, Folder 35)
      - Pezzini, Antonio, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 36)
      - Phayer, J. Michael, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 37)
      - Phillips, Peggy A., 1992-1994 (Box 38, Folder 38)
      - Piehler, G. Kurt, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 39)
      - Pike, David, 1986-1993 (Box 38, Folder 40)
      - Pines, Burton Yale, 1960-1972 (Box 38, Folder 41)
      - Pinto, António Costa, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 42)
      - Pois, Robert A., 1962-1997 (Box 38, Folder 43)
      - Popkin, Jeremy D., 1980-1981, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 44)
      - Popkin, Richard Henry, 1976-1979, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 45)
      - Popp, Wolfgang, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 46)
      - Porter, Jack Nusan, 1982, 1984, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 47)
      - Prost, Antoine, 1993-1994 (Box 38, Folder 48)
      - Pryke, Sam, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 49)
      - Pulzer, Peter G. J., 1964 (Box 38, Folder 50)
      - Puhle, Hans-Jürgen, 1971-1976 (Box 38, Folder 51)
      - Quaresima, Leonardo, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 52)
      - Rabinbach, Anson, 1968-1979 (Box 38, Folder 53)
      - Rabinbach, Anson, 1980-1999 (Box 38, Folder 54)
      - Radkau, Joachim, 1996, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 55)
      - Ranum, Orest A., 1996 (Box 38, Folder 56)
      - Ras, Marion E. P. de, 1988-1993 (Box 38, Folder 57)
      - Rearick, Charles, 1973, 1980-1981, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 58)
      - Reichert, Klaus, 1991, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 59)
      - Reid, James J., 1988, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 60)
      - Reinharz, Jehuda, 1978-1981, 1990-1997 (Box 38, Folder 61)
      - Rémond, René, 1968-1969 (Box 38, Folder 62)
      - Reszler, André, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 63)
      - Revid, Benjamin, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 64)
      - Rice-Maximin, Edward Francis, 1996-1998 (Box 38, Folder 65)
      - Richardson, Malcolm, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 66)
      - Riney-Kehrberg, Pamela, 1992-1999 (Box 38, Folder 67)
      - Ringer, Alexander L., 1979 (Box 38, Folder 68)
      - Ringer, Fritz K., 1969-1972 (Box 38, Folder 69)
      - Rockaway, Robert A., 1977 (Box 38, Folder 70)
      - Root, Winfred Trexler, undated (Box 38, Folder 71)
      - Rose, Alison, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 72)
      - Rose, Paul Lawrence, 1981, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 73)
      - Ruderman, David B., 1988 (Box 38, Folder 74)
      - Ruigh, Robert E., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 75)
      - Runge, Irene, 1983-1999 (Box 38, Folder 76)
      - Ryszka, Franciszek, 1981-1982 (Box 38, Folder 77)
      - Saal, Ellen, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 78)
      - Sabath, Rachel T., 1988 (Box 38, Folder 79)
      - Sabean, David Warren, 1964-1970 (Box 38, Folder 80)
      - Sabean, David Warren, 1971-1998 (Box 38, Folder 81)
      - Sadkovich, James J., 1975-1990 (Box 38, Folder 82)
      - Sakai, Yukichi, 1975-1980 (Box 38, Folder 83)
      - Salzmann, Hans M., 1957 (Box 38, Folder 84)
      - Samuelson, Arthur, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 85)
      - Saposnik, Bruce, 1998-1999 (Box 38, Folder 86)
      - Schalk, David L., 1985, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 87)
      - Schieder, Wolfgang, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 88)
      - Schewe, Douglas, 1997-1998 (Box 38, Folder 89)
      - Schilfert, Gerhard, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 90)
      - Schneider, Jeffrey A., 1995-1997 (Box 38, Folder 91)
      - Schnapp, Jeffrey T. (Jeffrey Thompson), 1993-1997 (Box 38, Folder 92)
      - Schoenbaum, David, 1972-1979, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 93)
      - Scholem, Gershom Gerhard, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 94)
      - Schorsch, Ismar, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 95)
      - Schorske, Carl E., 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 96)
      - Schrader, Stefan, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 97)
      - Schubert, Dirk, 1983, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 98)
      - Schwegman, Marjan, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 99)
      - Scott, Joan Wallach, 1973-1976 (Box 38, Folder 100)
      - Segrè, Claudio G., 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 101)
      - Seidler, Victor J., 1993 (Box 38, Folder 102)
      - Selby, Werner J., 1993-1996 (Box 38, Folder 103)
      - Shachar, Isaiah, 1962, 1968-1977 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Shain, Milton, 1980-1981, 1993-1995 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Shaltiel, Eli, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Shapira, Anita, 1996-1998 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Shapiro, Stanley, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Sheehan, James J., 1964-1993 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Shenhar-Alroy, Aliza, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Shimoni, Gideon, 1974, 1980, 1990-1998 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Shirakawa, Sam H., 1992 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Shmueli, Aviel, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Siegel, Paul, undated, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Silverglate, Jesse Joseph, 1970-1977 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Simon, H. J., 1952 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Siro, Livio, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Sivan, Emmanuel, 1973-1995 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Skidmore, Thomas E., 1975 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Sklar, Martin J., 1990-1998 (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - Skloot, Robert, 1979, 1993-1996 (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - Sluhovsky, Moshe, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Small, Helen, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - Smelser, Ronald M., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - Smit, Mathijs, 1995-1996 (Box 39, Folder 22)
      - Smith, Harvey, 1974-1985 (Box 39, Folder 23)
      - Söder, Hans-Peter, 1990-1995 (Box 39, Folder 24)
      - Solmsen, Lilo (Lieselotte?), 1989 (Box 39, Folder 25)
      - Soloway, Richard A., 1955-1969 (Box 39, Folder 26)
      - Soloway, Richard A., 1970-1998 (Box 39, Folder 27)
      - Solt, Leo F. (Leo Frank), 1958-1970 (Box 39, Folder 28)
      - Sommer, Doris, 1973, 1978, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 29)
      - Sorkin, David Jan, 1974-1996 (Box 39, Folder 30)
      - Sorum, Paul Clay, 1970-1975 (Box 39, Folder 31)
      - Soucy, Robert, 1970-1997 (Box 39, Folder 32)
      - Soucy, Robert, 1862-1969 (Box 39, Folder 33)
      - Sowerwine, Charles, 1970-1981 (Box 39, Folder 34)
      - Spackman, Barbara, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 35)
      - Speer, Albert, 1971-1977 (Box 39, Folder 36)
      - Spielmann, Diane R., 1993 (Box 39, Folder 37)
      - Spitz, Lewis William, 1967-1968 (Box 39, Folder 38)
      - Spock, Claire, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 39)
      - Staderini, Alessandra, 1984-1985, 1995-1998 (Box 39, Folder 40)
      - Steakley, James D., 1981-1997 (Box 39, Folder 41)
      - Steckhan, Otto, 1961, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 42)
      - Steinberg, David A., undated, 1976-1978 (Box 39, Folder 43)
      - Steinberg, Elizabeth, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 44)
      - Stern, Frank, 1991-1993 (Box 39, Folder 45)
      - Sternhell, Zeev, 1970-1997 (Box 39, Folder 46)
      - Stewart, Charles, 1993, 199 (Box 39, Folder 47)
      - Stolpe, Elmar, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 48)
      - Stoltzfus, Nathan, 1993-1995 (Box 39, Folder 49)
      - Stolz, Gerd, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 50)
      - Strassler, David, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 51)
      - Strauch, Hans D., 1995-1996 (Box 39, Folder 52)
      - Stromberg, Roland N., 1979 (Box 39, Folder 53)
      - Sturani, Enrico, 1995-1998 (Box 39, Folder 54)
      - Suzzi Valli, Roberta, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 55)
      - Sylvers, Malcolm, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 56)
      - Sznajder, Mario, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 57)
      - Tal, Uriel, 1970-1983 (Box 39, Folder 58)
      - Talmon, J. L. (Jacob Leib), 1979, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 59)
      - Tame, Peter D., 1987, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 60)
      - Tarrow, Susan, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 61)
      - Tatz, Colin Martin, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 62)
      - Tauber, Alfred I., 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 63)
      - Taylor, Robert R., 1985 (Box 39, Folder 64)
      - Teveth, Shabtai, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 65)
      - Thayer, John Alden, 1962-1985 (Box 39, Folder 66)
      - Ticktin, Max, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 67)
      - Till, Karen E., 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 68)
      - Toft, Daniel, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 69)
      - Tommasi, Rodolfo, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 70)
      - Tootalian, Patricia E., 1979 (Box 39, Folder 71)
      - Toscano, Mario, 1989-1995 (Box 39, Folder 72)
      - Traina, Richard P., 1996 (Box 39, Folder 73)
      - Treitel, Corinna, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 74)
      - Treschan, Victor, 1974-1983 (Box 39, Folder 75)
      - Trinterud, Leonard J., 1955 (Box 39, Folder 76)
      - Troen, S. Ilan (Selwyn Ilan), 1995-1996 (Box 39, Folder 77)
      - Truman, Joel S., 1970?-1979 (Box 39, Folder 78)
      - Tucker, Scott, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 79)
      - Tugendhat, Ernst, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 80)
      - Tuinebreyer, Wilco, 1994, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 81)
      - Turner, Norma B., 1991 (Box 39, Folder 82)
      - Tweton, D. Jerome, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 83)
      - Ullstein, Frederick, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 84)
      - Umstätter, Hans, 1951 (Box 39, Folder 85)
      - Uran, Steven, 1972-1984, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 86)
      - Vago, Bela, 1972-1981 (Box 39, Folder 87)
      - Van Creveld, Martin L., 1985, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 88)
      - Vasconcellos, John, 1970, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 89)
      - Vaudagna, Maurizio, 1988, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 90)
      - Vierhaus, Rudolf, 1981-1987 (Box 39, Folder 91)
      - Villa, Brian Loring, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 92)
      - Vineberg, Yisrael, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 93)
      - Vogtherr, Christoph Martin, 1996-1997 (Box 39, Folder 94)
      - Volkov, Shulamit, 1985-1996 (Box 39, Folder 95)
      - Vondung, Klaus, 1975-199640 (Box 39, Folder 96)
      - Wagner, Jonathan F. (Jonathan Frederick), 1974 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Walzer, Michael, 1972, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Wangermann, Ernst, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Wassermann, Henry, 1982-1988 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Weber, Eugen Joseph, 1955-1998 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Weigel, Sigrid, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Weinberg, David H., 1970-1998 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Weinberg, Gerhard L., 1992, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Weinberg, Robert, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Weiner, Ruth A., 1996 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Weinstein, Donald, 1951-1969 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Weinstein, Laurence A., 1990-1991 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Wheeler, Douglas L., 1994 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Whitfield, Stephen J., 1985 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Wiedmann, August K., 1995 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - Wiese, James Andrew, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Wilcox, William B., 1957 (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Williams, William Appleman?, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Winter, J. M., 1972-1998 (Box 40, Folder 19)
      - Winterhalter, Cecilia, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - Winternitz, Judith, 1979-1984 (Box 40, Folder 21)
      - Wistrich, Robert S., 1978, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - Wittenstein, George J., 1994-1997, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Wolf, Hans, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - Wolf, Heinz, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 25)
      - Wolf, John B. (John Baptiste), 1965-1969 (Box 40, Folder 26)
      - Wolfson, Manfred, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 27)
      - Woodruff, Nan Elizabeth, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 28)
      - Woolf, S. J. (Stuart Joseph), 1985 (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - Woude, A. M. van der, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 30)